The magic is back!
Lethal Weapon 2 is a action, adventure, comedy film directed by Richard Donner.
Riggs and Murtaugh are on the trail of South African diplomats
using their immunity to engage in criminal activities.
Martin Riggs, played by Mel Gibson.
Roger Murtaugh, played by Danny Glover.
Leo Getz, played by Joe Pesci.
Arjen Rudd, played by Joss Ackland.
Pieter Vorstedt, played by Derrick O'Connor.
Rika Van Den Haas, played by Patsy Kensit.
Lethal Weapon 2 is a 1989 American buddy cop action comedy film directed by Richard Donner, and starring
Mel Gibson, Danny Glover, Joe Pesci, Joss Ackland, Derrick O'Connor and Patsy Kensit.
It is a sequel to the 1987 film Lethal Weapon and the second
installment in the Lethal Weapon film series.
Gibson and Glover respectively reprise their roles as LAPD officers Martin Riggs and Roger Murtaugh, who protect an irritating
federal witness (Pesci), while taking on a gang of South African drug smugglers hiding behind diplomatic immunity.
The film was nominated for an Academy Award for
Best Sound Editing (for Robert G.
Henderson).
The film received mostly positive reviews and earned
more than $227 million worldwide.
The film is followed by Lethal Weapon 3.
The film explores themes of showdown, police, loss of
loved one, sequel, mixed martial arts (mma).
The tone is lighthearted and intense.